[
  {
    "question": "Difficult",
    "answer": "すずしい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Easy",
    "answer": "かんたん",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cute",
    "answer": "かわいい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fun",
    "answer": "たのしい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Busy",
    "answer": "いそがしい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Free/ Unoccupied",
    "answer": "ひま",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wide",
    "answer": "ひろい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Narrow",
    "answer": "せまい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Far",
    "answer": "とおい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nearby",
    "answer": "ちかい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "A lot",
    "answer": "おおい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Few",
    "answer": "すくない",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Long",
    "answer": "ながい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Short",
    "answer": "みじかい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stressful",
    "answer": "たいへん",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sleepy/ Boring",
    "answer": "ねむい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 2"
  }
]